(Stuart:)Can you please get back
to the drunk girl?
(Stuart:)I'd like something to think
about in the shower.
(Zack:)Oh, yeah.
(Zack:)Right. Anyway, she takes off
all of her clothes,
(Zack:)climbs into the hot tub,
and the first thing I notice...
(Sheldon:)The water level rose.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)Of course it did.
(Sheldon:)It's said that Archimedes,
(Sheldon:)the ancient Greek mathematician,
(Sheldon:)discovered the principle
of displacement
(Sheldon:)while taking a bath.
Terrific.
Go ahead, Zack.
Naked drunk girl,
free-balling, continue.
(Sheldon:)Forgive me,
but I think you'll find
(Sheldon:)my story is
more interesting.
(Barry:)Does yours
have wet breasts in it?
(Sheldon:)Better.
(Sheldon:)It has a gold crown.
(Sheldon:)You see, the king
(Sheldon:)wondered how much gold was in it
(Sheldon:)and charged Archimedes with
coming up with the solution.
(Sheldon:)Because the crown was
irregularly shaped,
(Sheldon:)there was no way
to mathematically
(Sheldon:)determine its volume.
(Sheldon:)But, while bathing,
Archimedes realized
(Sheldon:)he could immerse the crown
(Sheldon:)and measure the amount
the water rose.